<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" ?>
<wamp>
<instance title="CREATING A HABITABLE ENVIRONMENT">
<context>
Humans have many basic needs and one of them is to have an environment that can sustain their lives. Our current population is 6 billion people and it is still growing exponentially. This will, if not already, caused problems as there are very limited spaces for us. The solution can be obtain by using technology to achieve a better usage of space that we have and resolve the problems in lands that inhospitable such as desserts and swamps.
<![CDATA[<br/><br/>]]>
Some countries are having difficulties in managing a place to live for their citizen as they tend to get overpopulated. This caused problem like the appearance of slums which most of the time is not safe due to the unhealthy environment. The only way to satisfy the increasing demands of space is by achieving a better usage of the land like designing taller building so it can accommodate more number of people with the same spaces. It is also important to create a better material that can support the buildings despite any natural disaster like earthquakes. A good example is Japan where there are a lot of tall condominiums despite the large number of earthquakes happening in there. Besides a better usage of lands, a better sanitation is also needed because a huge number of people need a clean environment to maintain their heath. For example, countries in Africa can accommodate more people if they can manage to design a better sanitation system.
</context>
</instance>
<instance title="The Factors that Shaped Biometrics">
<context>
Identification has become more and more important in our society. Thanks to biometric identification, nowadays, we can open a locked door without keys, withdraw money from the bank without entering password, and travel around the world without taking various cards. Biometrics, by definition, refers to technologies of measurement and analysis of human body characteristics. These characteristics include fingerprints, eye retinas and irises, voice patterns, facial patterns and hand measurements. Besides some technologically determinists that allow the development of biometric identification, this technology is also shaped by three social factors, namely, the desire of the society for safety, convenience and economy.
<![CDATA[<br/><br/>]]>
Safety is one of the crucial problems that many countries and companies concern. On one hand more and more virus and hack can access personal computers, so the secret data and documents may be stolen. On the other hand, some important departments need strict administration to their members to avoid information leaks. The United States Department of Defense (DoD) {Common Access Card}[HYPERLINK: http://en.wikipedia.org/wiki/Common_Access_Card] is a successful use of biometric identification. This card contains biometric data to add security and reduce the risk of falsification (Ben, 2008). As we can see, the biometric identification involved in important secure areas is designed to identify human with accuracy and reliability.
</context>
</instance>
<instance title="China's problems hampering engineering design processes for innovations">
<context>
Since the reform and open policy in 1970's, China has been eagerly speeding up on its way to industrialization and flourish. Although the improvement is apparent, there are still a number of problems hampering engineering design processes for innovations. Among them, education system and perception of innovation stand out becoming two major difficulties.
<![CDATA[<br/><br/>]]>
As Dr. Ronald B. Standler pointed out in 1998, creativity is very important in science and engineering. Drs Wayne Hall and Paul Robinson from University of Plymouth also found out that " Engineering + Creativity = Employability for Graduates". However, China's examination-oriented education system deeply throttles students' creativity. Not only parents and annotators but also whole society pushes students concentrating on how to get outstanding marks in examinations. Students spend most of their time reciting details in text books and doing tedious exercises again and again for the simple reason that these can help them get familiar with examinations. As a result, students have no chance to develop their creative thinking and gradually become stereotype.
</context>
</instance>
</wamp>
